[Music]
at fwd we know that spending on life
protection is less of a priority when
you're building your life
saving for your kids education and
maintaining a comfy lifestyle
and these priorities are exactly why we
think life protection matters most to
you
because you will want your dependents to
be taken care of even if you're
seriously ill or if you pass on
lia protection gap studies have shown an
average adult needs a life insurance
coverage of
9 to 10 times your annual income for an
average singaporean there will be a
coverage of around 550 000
fwd term life plus insurance makes it
easy and affordable to get protected
without sacrificing your priorities you
can buy a one million dollar coverage
online in minutes from as low as one
dollar a day
with no medical checkups required
flexible premium options are available
too
choose to expand your protection with
these benefits your spouse will also get
free term life protection of up to 250
in the case of your unfortunate passing
get a quote now